Ghost Meets Gal!
The school entrance ceremony is pretty boring, isn’t it?
I agree....
Now our principal would deliver a welcoming speech.
So that person is....
Greetings to our freshmen this year,
I am the school principal Krysrain.
This academy is the place that gathers idols-in-training who are coming from different nations and races,
and those with different quirks will improve through competitions.
I am looking forward to witnessing the very best idol arise from you.
Here are always students being enrolled here every year, right?
Yes.
How many years does it take to complete the curriculum though?
Huh?
Speaking of which, does the concept of “graduation” even exist here to begin with?
So hypothetically if we get to stay here until we become granny....do we get to debut as “granny idol”?
Since I am a Ghost, so I will not age at all.
What the heck?! I am so jealous of you!
So...that means you will not die even if you hit the so-called life expectancy?
Since I am a Ghost....so technically I am already dead.
Heh....for real?
I am sorry for your loss....
I am quite humbled.
(Inside the dormitory)
Coming up is our introduction to the dormitory.
Y..yes!
I wonder who I will end up sharing the room with?
Speak of which, I went shopping immediately after getting the nails done...
I see...
so I may not end up in the same room with Santhi-chan...
so that means I gotta speak with new strangers....
Ahhhh!
what happen if I end up meeting scary folks?!
Eeek....I am getting nervous now!
So, that unpopped thingy from popcorns end up getting into my eyes....
Eh?
Lubna-chi?
She disappeared again!
I...I am sorry!
Ah! You are here!
I have disappeared again due to extreme nervousness....
Does my topic making people THAT nervous?
Looking down, sighing,
hiding my true feelings
Every time i step forward,
even if i'm trembling,
I can't lie to my desire of change!
It's surely a distant dream right now,
but i want to chase it together!
Even if our futures are different colors,
Let's paint them with the same dream.
Because you are the one who gives me courage!